Master, please give me your penis.
ご主人様、おちんちんくださいって
Look at the camera too.
カメラも見て
Master, please put your penis in me.
ご主人様、おちんちん入れてくださいって
Students and chins are also attached, right?
学生と顎もつけてるんだろう?
Only with my uncle.
おじさんとだけだな
A pike icon will appear.
パイクアイコン出るぞ
Master, please give me your penis.
ご主人様、おちんちんください
what happened?
どうしたの?
Do you think you will always help me?
いつも手伝ってくださると思ってる?
Great, I'll help you.
いいね、手伝うよ
You can feel it a lot.
いっぱい感じていいからな
Isn't it called station time?
なんだ、駅タイムっていうじゃないか
I'll go again.
もう一度行くんだ
I have to punish you.
お仕置きしないといけないな
Cheer up, ass.
気を出してくれ、おしり
Let me put you on the bed.
ベッドにおしりつけさせてくれ
No, that's fine.
いや、そこでいいな
It's here.
ここだ
Does it feel nostalgic?
懐かしいのかな?
Please sit on the bed.
ベッドに座ってくれ
Because it will come out to everyone.
みんなに出てくるからな
Open everything up, come on.
全部開放しちゃえ、ほら
You don't have to worry about that.
気にしなくていいぞ、そんなもん
Why are you doing this?
なんでされてんの?
Let me give you a hard workout from your butt.
おしりから激しいお疲れさせてもらおう
Severe fatigue from the buttocks
お しりから激しいお疲れ
Let me do it.
さ せてもらおう
Do you want me to stop?
やめてほしい?
Do you want more?
もっとついてほしい?
It's the one that was in Tubun's Manko.
ツブンのマンコウに入ってたやつだよな
feel ill?
気持ち悪い?
I'm strong though.
だいじょうは強いけど
What does it taste like?
どんな味がする?
Let me take it off your hands.
手に離してもらおう
Talking.
口立て